scalado.com 2009-04-02

# privacy policy

Privacy is an important issue for visitors to the Scalado web site [www.scalado.com](http://www.scalado.com/). The following information is designed to help visitors understand what information Scalado gathers from the site, and how it handles the information once gathered.

 **Information collection and use  
** Scalado is the sole owner of any information collected on this site. Scalado will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Scalado may collect information from its users at several different points on its website. Scalado may transfer the information collected to any relevant unit within Scalado.

 **General Enquiries  
** If a user contacts Scalado with a general enquiry, the user may provide Scalado with personal information (for example contact details). Scalado will use this personal information to respond to the enquiry and track further correspondence. Information is also used to compile statistics on response handling, etc. This is done in aggregate, and no individual names or other personal information are retained. Personal information collected is not used for any other purpose.

 **Orders, surveys and contests  
** Scalado requests information from the user on its order form. Here a user must provide contact information and financial information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If Scalado has trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

From time to time Scalado's site may request information from users via contests or surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

 **Individuals' use of extranet  
** Extranets provide customer specific content and functions. In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to Scalado's major customers, Scalado must mutually agree on which of their personnel may use specific extranet functions. Scalado uses cookies, together with additional security mechanisms, to identify and track the registered users who enter extranet portions of [www.scalado.com](http://www.scalado.com/) **External links**  
This web site may contain links to other sites. Scalado is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

 **Changes to Scalado's Internet privacy policy  
** Scalado may from time to time, make changes to this policy.
